http://www.sads.org/privacy-policy

Welcome to the new SADS site.
Click Here to report any problems.
SADS Foundation Hong Kong
Search for:
Log in
Supporting Families.
Saving Lives.
Sign-up for our Enewsletter here.
Library
AdvocacySchoolsMedical ProfessionalsGet InvolvedLiving with SADSResearch
Home |
privacy policy
This is the Sudden Arrhythmia Death Syndromes (SADS) Foundation Internet Privacy Notice, which discloses the privacy practices for www.stopsads.org.
Our Commitment to You
The Sudden Arrhythmia Death Syndromes (SADS) Foundation values your privacy and recognizes the sensitivity of your personal information. We have carefully crafted our privacy policy to address any concerns you might have, and to assure you that your personal information, if provided to us, will be treated carefully and appropriately.
Information Collection and Use
The Sudden Arrhythmia Death Syndromes (SADS) Foundation is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. We will not sell, share, or rent this information without your permission, or in ways other than those outlined in this statement. The Coalition collects information from visitors at several different points on our site. Personal information provided by you will be used to improve our web site and provide you with a more personalized experience.
Information that identifies you as a specific individual will not be disclosed to others without your permission, unless the disclosure is necessary to provide services that you have requested. We will not ask your permission to collect or use aggregate information about web site visitors or users of our products or services, since aggregate information does not identify you as a specific individual. In addition to these general provisions, we collect and use personal information in the following ways:
Choice/Opt-out
We may from time to time send you information about our programs, products and services via e-mail messages. If you no longer wish to receive our e-mail newsletters or promotional messages, you may opt-out of receiving these communications by following the "unsubscribe" instructions in the e-mail message.
Links
The Sudden Arrhythmia Death Syndromes (SADS) Foundation web site contains links to other sites. The Sudden Arrhythmia Death Syndromes (SADS) Foundation is not responsible for the privacy practices of such sites. We encourage you to be aware when you leave our site and to read the privacy statements of every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy notice applies solely to information collected on our web site.
Security of Your Information
We will take every precaution to protect your personal information. All personal information collected on individuals will be kept confidential and in a secure environment. Access to personal information will be restricted to only those personnel with a legitimate business purpose. Servers used to store personally identifiable information will be kept in a secure environment.
Changes in our Privacy Policy
Any changes to our Privacy Policy will be incorporated here so that you are always aware of the information we collect, the ways we use it, and any circumstances under which we disclose it. We may also contact you by e-mail to inform you of significant changes.
How to Contact Us
We invite your comments and questions about our web site, your experience with our site and services, and our Privacy Policy. You can reach us via
This e-mail address is being protected from spam bots, you need JavaScript enabled to view it or you can also contact us at 801-531-0937.
TSADonateAbout UsAdvocacyInternational PartnersSchoolsDropboxMedical ProfessionalsGet InvolvedLibraryLiving with SADSMatReqTestMedical Professional EducationNewsPress RoomResearchPaypal SuccessPaypal FailureThank you for your donation!Volunteer to Fight SADS!Overview of SADS Conditions
Online Community
SADS Online Support Community
Share Your Story
Stories: Living & Thriving with SADS
Stories: Forever in our Hearts
Enews Archives & Sign up
Find it Fast
Family Registration & Request Materials
Family history of unexpected, unexplained sudden death under age 40.
Fainting or seizure during exercise, excitement or startle.
Consistent or unusual chest pain &/or shortness of breath during exercise.
COPYRIGHT ©2011-2017 Sudden Arrhythmia Death Syndromes Foundation
4527 South 2300 East, Suite 104 | Salt Lake City, Utah 84117
Patient Support Line - (801) 948-0654
Office - (801) 272-3023
